# PRIYA BHADURIA

Digital Marketer

## **PROFILE**

A talented and passionate digital marketer with hands-on experience in Google Analytics, SEO and other social marketing platforms tools. Exceptional operation management skills with a strong ability to work independently and compelling communication with great interpersonal skills.



**JAIPUR** 



PRIYA.MJRP@GMAIL.COM



+91-9928338721



### **EDUCATION**

Master Of Science: Information Technology University of Rajasthan 2016

Bachelor Of Science: Information Technology MJRP University 2013

# SKILLS

GOOGLE ANALYTICS

SMS/EMAIL MARKETING

**GOOGLE ADS** 

OPERATION MANAGEMENT

HTML

# SEO

SOCIAL MEDIA

**EXPERTISE** 

FACEBOOK CAMPAIGNS

CUSTOMER SERVICE

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### MANAGER

- Boosted traffic to the website by approx. 35% from 5000 to 8000.
- Directed execution of performance campaigns that increased the ROAS by 40% and average conversation rates by 50%.
- Defined and implemented group social media strategy, increasing community size by over 200%.
- Created alternative business plans to improve customer relationships.
- Increased Facebook, Instagram followers, and engagement by 200%.
- Day-to-day social media content management for otootuitions.com.
- Increased monthly sales from more than 10 times in less than 6 months.

PADHAI HELP PVT. LTD.

2019-2021

## **EXPERIENCE**

## CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE

- Conferred with customers about concerns with products or services to resolve problems and drive sales.
- Amazon.us offshore merchant support and Website content Management.
- Informed customers about special promotions and provided detailed information for various products.

TELEPERFOR MANCE

2018-2019

# MARKETING AND COMMUNICATIONS MANAGER

- SEO/SMM for JECC website, social media platforms, website hygiene.
- · Aligned activities with corporate objectives by coordinating marketing, sales, and IT processes.
- · Oversaw preparation of marketing copy, images, videos, emails, and other collateral.
- · Client Servicing Data analysis and Reporting
- Event Management: Crossblade Concert, JJS, JAS
- · Analyzed and reported marketing data, including trends, web traffic patterns, and engagement.

JAIPUR
EXHIBITION
AND
CONVENTION
CENTER,

2017-2018

#### DIGITAL MARKETING ANALYST

- Analyze the key performance issue and helps in new client acquisition in a meaningful way.
- Initiated market research studies and analyzed findings.
- Worked with team to design organic campaigns and Email marketing campaigns to increase website traffic and sales.
- Researched, analyzed, and reported keyword optimization and trends.
- Managed organic and paid social media content campaigns to build a customer base, including content ideation, photography, and community engagement.
- Monitored and analyzed campaigns to determine success.
- Wrote blog content that increased audience engagement by 5% each month.
- Regularly updated and managed company website.

RMG MART INDIA PVT LTD

2016-2017